https://rrecord.com/privacy-policy/

your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
The Rappahannock Record Privacy Policy
The Rappahannock Record has a firm commitment to privacy. We take your privacy concerns seriously and want to make every effort to address them. That is why we have adopted the following policy, which explains our position on information-gathering and disclosure.
When you browse our website, information may be collected that identifies the pages that you visit, including the date and time of your visit, your geographical location and your service provider’s identity. This information helps us determine our audience and improve our service to the community.
Your name and personal information is not given to us by our server or others unless you choose to provide it by subscribing or placing an advertisement or submitting content or comments.
We do not disclose any personal information to a third party for marketing purposes.
The website may contain hyperlinks to websites other than the Rappahannock Record. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only. These other sites may have separate data and privacy practices and therefore we are not responsible for their policies or actions.
We will post any substantial changes in this privacy policy at least 30 days prior to the change taking effect.
If you have questions about this policy or feel that we have acted in violation of this policy, please contact mail@RRecord.com or write:
The Rappahannock Record
P.O. Box 400
Kilmarnock, VA 22482
(804) 435-1701
Customer Service
Circulation
Advertise
Other Services Contact UsSubmit NewsObituary GuidelinesLetter GuidelinesPress release guidelinesSubscribe/RenewNewsstandsDisplayClassifiedsDigitalSupplemental PublicationsPublic NoticesPrinting NeedsPurchase PhotosP.O. Box 400 • 27 N. Main St. • Kilmarnock, VA 22482 • 804-435-1701Advertise with us online. Rrecord.com receives over 200,000 page views each month!
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Rappahannock Record
